etonshirts.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy & Cookies | Eton Shirts US

We respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting your personal information. We have adopted a corporate wide Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information that you provide us with. The following information is provided by Eton to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. By registering at www.etonshirts.com, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions. 

If you are under 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about Eton's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering or placing an order with Eton. This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or organisations to which we link and Eton is not responsible for any personal information you submit to third parties via our website. Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy of such other companies or organisations before submitting your details.

### What personal information do we collect from you and how?

Eton collects personal information in several ways when you place an order or register for a service offered by Eton. By registering, you are consenting to the collection of your personal data. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping and credit/debit card billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfil your order. Saved card details will never be shared with third parties and will only be used to process your order, using our Payment Service Provider's systems. We may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

### What about cookies?

Our site uses cookies (very small files that are sent by us to your computer or other access devices) which we can access when you visit our site in future.

There are four types of cookies:

_Website functionality cookies_

__These cookies enable you to browse the website and use our features such as shopping baskets and wish lists.

_Website analytics cookies_

We use these cookies to measure and analyse how our customers use the website. This allows us to continuously improve our website and your shopping experience.

_Customer preference cookies_

When browsing or shopping online, the website will remember preferences you make (for example your user name, language or location). This makes your browsing experience simpler, easier and more personal to you.

_Targeting cookies or advertising cookies_

These cookies are used to deliver adverts relevant to you. In addition, they limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as helping us measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.  
By using our website you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device and access them when you visit the site in the future.  
If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the help and support area on your internet browser for instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.

_Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available[here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site._

### Our Cookies

#### **Name**

| 

#### **Source**

| 

#### **TTL browser**

| 

#### **Usage**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
_ga

| 

Google Analytics

|  | 

This is used to collect information about how visitors use the site  
  
_gat_UA-#

| 

Google Analytics

|  | 

This is used to collect information about how visitors use the site  
  
_gcl_au

| 

Google Analytics

|  | 

This is used to collect information about how visitors use the site  
  
_gid

| 

Google Analytics

|  | 

This is used to collect information about how visitors use the site  
  
_dc_gtm_UA-#

| 

Google Analytics

|  | 

This is used to collect information about how visitors use the site  
  
IDE

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
NID

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
1P_JAR

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
DSID

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
HSID

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
SID

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
SIDCC

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
SSID

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
SAPISID

| 

Google

|  | 

Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes  
  
_fbp

| 

Facebook

|  | 

Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.  
  
fr

| 

Facebook

|  | 

Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.  
  
tr

| 

Facebook

|  | 

Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.  
  
bcookie

| 

Linkedin

|  | 

Used by the social networking service, LinkedIn, for tracking the use of embedded services.  
  
BizoID

| 

Linkedin

|  | 

Used to track visitors on multiple websites, in order to present relevant ad vertisement based on the visitor's preferences.  
  
lidc

| 

Linkedin

|  | 

Used by the social networking service, LinkedIn, for tracking the use of embedded services.  
  
UserMatchHistory

| 

Linkedin

|  | 

Provider: Linkedin.com  
  
uid

| 

Criteo

| 

12 months

| 

User identifier on Criteo network.  
  
optout

| 

Criteo

| 

5 years

| 

Optout cookie. Allows user to sign off some if the criteos service.  
  
uic

| 

Criteo

| 

6 months

| 

Identifies the context of the user. It allows us to understand the profitability of the user based on his browser history on etonshirts.com.  
  
zdi

| 

Criteo

| 

6 months

| 

Passback loop detection. It counts the nujmber of times that the user is passed on one specific zone.  
  
eid

| 

Criteo

| 

6 months

| 

External ID. It contains the user id of Criteos partners. It is used for the reselling of pump inventory.  
  
### How this information may be used, including anyone it might be shared with

Eton may use your personal information for the processing of orders, payments, and to provide you with a personalised shopping experience. We will also use your details to fulfil and deliver your orders and manage your account. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. Where there is a legal obligation to do so, we may disclose your information to any relevant regulatory body. We may also use your personal information to send you marketing updates but only ever in accordance with your preferences (as detailed in the next section). We do not sell your details to third party marketing companies. We do collate information about site traffic, sales, wish list, and other commercial information which we may pass on to third parties but this information does not include any information which can identify you personally.

Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor customer patterns so we can consistently improve our site design to better meet our visitors' needs.

_From time to time Eton may employ third party business partners to collect personal information or to undertake marketing activities on Eton's behalf. In such cases, these third parties will be subject to confidentiality agreements and instructed by Eton to comply fully with the Eton Privacy Policy.  
_

### Marketing opt-in and opt-out provision

When you register, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to our regular update service which will send you:

_(i) Email alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about Eton, our subsidiaries or selected business partners._

_(ii) Direct mail alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about Eton, our subsidiaries or selected business partners._

We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes. Marketing communications you subscribe to will only be sent by Eton.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail. Alternatively, you can change your email preferences or opt out of all emails by logging into My Account.

To opt out of direct mail service or updates, please contact an Eton customer care representative by email care@etonshirts.com or click unsubscribe in the footer of our promotional e-mails.

### How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information Eton maintains

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information held by Eton is not correct, please visit the website and after logging into the site using the "Sign In" menu on the home page, your personal information will be made available for review and change in the "My Account" section. Only you or, upon your request, the Customer Care department, may access your personal data from the website using your password and User ID. Information may be changed online within Account Details, Address Book, and My Email Preferences. You can change or delete saved credit/debit card details each time you make a purchase. You will also be able to delete saved credit/debit card details by adding or editing a shipping/billing address. If you change your billing or shipping address while your order is still being processed, the order will be re-processed through security validation checks. If you prefer, you may contact us by email at care@etonshirts.com and we will amend your personal details.

### Your rights

You have the right to get information when and how your personal data are being processed and have control over your information. You also have the right to have your information corrected if our data for any reason is wrong, in certain instances you also have the right to have the data deleted or blocked. You also have the right to have the data moved or take out your information.

If you are under 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about Eton's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering or placing an order with Eton.

The data controller is Eton AB, Stora vägen 8, 507 71 Gånghester, Sweden. For any questions, objections or requests please contact us at care@etonshirts.com

_Eton has appointed a Data Protection Officer, Gunilla Dahlqwist, who can be reached at  [dpo@etonshirts.com](mailto:dpo@etonshirts.com)_

### Safeguarding your personally identifiable information

We will take reasonable steps to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. When you place an order or access your account information, we use a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption which encrypts your information before it is sent to us, to protect it from unauthorised use. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third party business partners' to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.

### Where and how to ask questions or file complaints

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the help section of the web site where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered. If you require more information please go to the Contact Us section of the web site and send an email to the relevant Eton department. If you wish to talk to a Eton customer care representative please email care@etonshirts.com. In case you feel that we've processed your data in a non-compliant way you can always contact us. You can also lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. Eton AB is under the jurisdiction of the Swedish Data Protection Authority.
